{
    "id": "4efcaddb0c2f454d8fa9a646c8e91e82",
    "title": "Comparative And Superlative Adjectives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "95e9618ce073419493266aa7023bb645",
            "title": "Comparative And Superlative Adjectives",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Sam can run ……………………. than you.",
                    "description": "We need a comparative expression before than.",
                    "answers": [
                        "fast",
                        "faster",
                        "more fast",
                        "fastest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Raghu is …………………. than his friends.",
                    "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever.",
                    "answers": [
                        "more clever",
                        "cleverer",
                        "cleverest",
                        "most cleverest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are no ……………………. than him.",
                    "description": "Better is the comparative form of good. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "gooder",
                        "good",
                        "better"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was …………………….. than I thought.",
                    "description": "Easier is the comparative form of easy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "more easy",
                        "easier",
                        "easiest",
                        "more easiest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Lead is the ……………………… metal.",
                    "description": "We use the superlative to compare one thing with the whole group that it belongs to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "heavy",
                        "heavier",
                        "heaviest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "A rabbit is ……………………. than a deer.",
                    "description": "Smaller is the comparative form of small.",
                    "answers": [
                        "smaller",
                        "more small",
                        "smallest",
                        "most small"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ……………………… than that.",
                    "description": "More attractive is the comparative form of attractive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "attractiver",
                        "more attractive",
                        "most attractive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your voice is ………………….. than mine.",
                    "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "badder",
                        "worse",
                        "worser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She earns ……………………. money than I do.",
                    "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "less",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The …………………….. expensive holidays are often the best.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "least",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was not as intelligent as the others, but I was the …………………..",
                    "description": "Prettiest is the superlative form of pretty. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "prettiest",
                        "more pretty",
                        "most pretty"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "As you get older, you get …………………….",
                    "description": "In this structure we use a comparative in both clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "tolerant",
                        "more tolerant",
                        "most tolerant"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}